<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language title="English (EN)" date_format="M j, Y" time_format="g:i A" currency_format="{symbol}{value}" week_start="0" decimal_point="." thousands_separator="," label_separator=":" comma_separator=", " ellipsis="…" parenthesis_open="(" parenthesis_close=")" language_code="en-US" text_direction="LTR" user_selectable="1" addon_id="XF" base_version_id="2020770" export_version="2">
  <phrase title="extra_copyright" addon_id="XF" version_id="2020670" version_string="2.2.6"><![CDATA[Software by Xenforo | Style from Themehouse<br>
Follow us: <a href="https://space.bilibili.com/29023601" rel="nofollow">Bilibili</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/McShareTeam" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://github.com/SuperYYT" rel="nofollow">Github</a> | <a href="http://weibo.com/5679272983/" rel="nofollow">Weibo</a><br>
<script type="text/javascript">
    copyright=new Date();
    update=copyright.getFullYear();
    document.write("&copy; 2018-"+ update + " MineBBS All Rights Reserved");
</script>]]></phrase>
  <phrase title="terms_rules_text" addon_id="XF" version_id="2020270" version_string="2.2.2"><![CDATA[<p>1. Abide by the relevant laws and regulations of the people's Republic of China and local. </p>
<p>2. It is not allowed to publish any pornographic, illegal and harmful remarks on this website. </p>
<p>3. It is strictly forbidden to link illegal information such as politics, pornography, religion and superstition. </p>
<p>4. Bear all the civil or criminal liabilities directly or indirectly caused by your behavior. </p>
<p>5. Respect each other, abide by Internet ethics, and prohibit malicious attacks and abuse. </p>
<p>6. Administrators and moderators have the right to retain or delete any content in the forum, and have all management rights. </p>
<p>7. The content published on this website is directly published by the users of this website, which only represents the user's personal views. Any disputes and copyright issues arising from the user's views and positions shall be borne by the publisher. </p>
<p>8. This website shall be exempted from any loss caused by force majeure affecting the normal operation of the network, such as Internet attack, computer virus invasion or temporary shutdown caused by government regulation. </p>
<p>9. This site points only for entertainment virtual role, prohibit trading, has nothing to do with real wealth. </p>
<p>Although our administrators and moderators will try their best to remove all harmful information from the forum, we can't audit all the information. All the information represents the author's personal views and can't represent the "forum operator". </p>
<p>The owner of the website has the right to delete, edit, move and close any topic for any reason. Minebbs reserves the right of final interpretation of all terms. </p>]]></phrase>
</language>
